Guide to the John Hope Franklin papers, 1891-2010, bulk 1950-2010 RL.10029
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Service (S), 1941-2008; 26 boxes
  - National Council on the Humanities membership, 1976-1978 (Box S15)
  - National Council on the Humanities resignation, 1979 (Box S15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. National Humanities Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box S15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. Jefferson Lecturer, 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box S15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. Jefferson Lecture film with N. Kroll (Racial Equality in America), 1977-1981 (Box S15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. Jefferson Lecturer programs and publicity, 3 folders (Box S15)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. Jefferson Lectures publication comments, etc., 1976-1979 (Box S16)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities. Jefferson Lecture Nomination Committee, 1977-1981 (Box S16)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities research support, 1990-1992 (Box S16)
    Regarding Runaway Slaves project.
  - National Fair Housing Alliance, 2006 (Box S16)
  - National Geographic Magazine, 1984 (Box S16)
    Consultant for an article on the underground railroad.
  - National History Day Advisor, 1981-1991 (Box S16)
  - National Humanities Center Fellow, 1980 (Box S16)
  - National Humanities Center, 1980-2003, 5 folders (Box S16)
    General correspondence, memos, meeting agendas, and programs.
  - National Humanities Center Board of Trustees, 1985-1997, 4 folders (Box S16)
  - National Humanities Center Board of Trustees, 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box S16)
    Meeting books from October 2002 and March 2003 meetings.
  - National Museum of African American History and Culture. Congressional Acts, 1989 (Box S16)
  - National Museum of African American History and Culture. Collector's Passion exhibit, 2001-2002 (Box S16)
  - National Museum of African American History and Culture. Scholarly Advisory Committee, 2005-2008, 2 folders (Box S16)
  - National Museum of American History, 1995 (Box S16)
  - National Park System Advisory Board, 1999 (Box S16)
    General correspondence and memos.
  - National Park System Advisory Board. Board meetings and conferences, 2000, 2 folders (Box S16)
  - National Park System Advisory Board. Board meetings and conferences, 2000, 2 folders (Box S17)
  - National Park System Advisory Board travel reimbursement, 2000-2001 (Box S17)
  - National Park System Advisory Board. National Historic Landmark nominations, 2000 and undated, 4 folders (Box S17)
  - National Park System Advisory Board. Old Spanish Trail Report, 2000 (Box S17)
  - National Park System Advisory Board, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box S17)
    General correspondence, memos.
  - National Park System Advisory Board reports, 2001 (Box S17)
  - National Park System Advisory Board. Board meeting, 2001 (Box S17)
  - National Research Council, 1970-1974 (Box S17)
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans, 1984-1989 and undated, 6 folders (Box S17)
    Meeting materials and 1987 draft report.
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans research and reports, 1986 (Box S18)
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans. Internal activities, 1986 (Box S18)
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans. Draft report, 1987, 4 folders (Box S18)
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans. Study draft report, 1987-1988, 5 folders (Box S18)
  - National Research Council. Committee on the Status of Black Americans. Draft report feedback, 1988 (Box S18)
  - National Science Foundation, 1981 (Box S18)
  - National Spinal Cord Injury Association. Board of Directors, 1982-1983 (Box S18)
  - National Underground Railroad Freedom Center, 2005 (Box S17)
  - National Underground Railroad Freedom Center, 2005 (Box S18)
  - National Urban League, 1958-1981 (Box S18)
    Writings (including The Negro's Dilemma) and correspondence.
  - National Urban League, 1996-1999 and undated (Box S18)
  - National Visionary Leadership Project, 2002-2006 (Box S18)
  - National Visionary Leadership Project Board of Directors, 2005 (Box S18)
  - National Visionary Leadership Project Board of Directors, 2006-2007 (Box S19)
  - New York City Board of Education consultant, 1963 (Box S19)
  - New York City Housing and Redevelopment Board, 1962 (Box S19)
  - New York Public Library. Constitution Bicentennial Project, 1985-1987 (Box S19)
  - New York Public Library. Schomburg Commission for Preservation of Black Culture, 1987 (Box S19)
  - New York State Civil War Centennial Commission, 1961-1962 (Box S19)
  - New York State Historical Association, 1980 (Box S19)
  - NC African American Archives Group, 1989-1992 (Box S19)
  - NC Alliance for Democracy. NC Voters for Clean Elections Advisory Board, 2000 (Box S19)
  - NC Center for the Study of Black History, 1988-1990 (Box S19)
  - NC Central University, 1991-1993, 1995-2008 (Box S19)
  - NC Central University. Shepherd Memorial Library, 1995-2003 (Box S19)
  - NC College (now NC Central University). James E. Shepard Memorial Foundation, 1949 (Box S19)
  - NC Civil War Tourism Council, 1994-1996 (Box S19)
  - NC Coalition for a Moratorium, 2005 (Box S19)
  - NC Commission on US Constitution Bicentennial, 1986-1990 (Box S19)
  - NC Dept. of Cultural Resources Task Force, 1994-2001, 2 folders (Box S19)
    General correspondence, memos, meetings agendas, reports.
  - NC Freedom Monument Project Honorary Chair, 2002-2008 (Box S19)
    One CD containing electronic media has been separated from this folder. Please contact Research Services for assistance accessing that item.
  - NC High School of Social Studies advisor, 1991 (Box S19)
  - NC Institute of Minority Economic Development, 1989-1992 (Box S19)
  - NC Literary and Historical Association, 1979-1987 (Box S19)
  - NC Museum of Art, 2001-2003 (Box S19)
  - NC Museum of History. Associates Board of Directors, 1993-2006 (Box S19)
  - NC Museum of History. Civil Rights exhibit, 2001 (Box S19)
  - NC Museum of Life and Science identification cards, 2002 (Box S19)
  - NC Mutual Life Insurance centennial celebrations, 1998 (Box S19)
  - NC Public Television. America's Testament program, 1988 (Box S19)
  - NC State University Board of Visitors, 1992-1994 (Box S19)
  - NC State University Park Scholarship program, 2000 (Box S19)
  - North Caroliniana Society, 1987-2006 (Box S20)
  - North Carolinians for Gun Control, 1995 (Box S20)
  - North Tulsa Oral History Project, 1994 (Box S20)
  - Oklahoma Historical Society, 2000-2002 (Box S20)
  - Orchestral Association of Chicago Board of Trustees, 1976-1979 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1954-1962 (Box S20)
    Formerly the Mississippi Valley Historical Association.
  - Organization of American Historians, 1970-1973 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians bicentennial plans, 1973-1974 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians. Committees, 1974-1975 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians Convention, 1976 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians, 1975-1982 (Box S20)
    Re: Franklin's presidency, 1973-1974.
  - Organization of American Historians, 1988-1993, 2005-2007 (Box S20)
  - Organization of American Historians annual meeting, 2002 (Box S20)
  - Patterson vs. McLean Credit Union. Amicus Curie brief, 1987 (Box S20)
  - PBS. The American Experience. Africans in America, 1990-1993 (Box S20)
  - PEN American Center, 1998-1999 (Box S20)
  - Phelps-Stoke Conference on Negro Life, 1956 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1957-2002, 4 folders (Box S20)
    General materials, including meeting notes, bulletins, and correspondence.
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Triennial meetings, 1970-1988 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Committee on Nominations, 1972-1988 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Oratorio, 1973-1976 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Executive Committee, 1973-1982, 2 folders (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Constitution revision, 1973-1985 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Franklin's election to presidency, 1974 (Box S20)
    Congratulatory notes.
  - Phi Beta Kappa. Franklin's presidency, 1973-1976 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1973-1979 (Box S20)
    Re: new chapters, membership.
  - Phi Beta Kappa Bicentennial Committee, 1974-1976 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa awards, 1974-1984 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa film series, 1975 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Bicentennial Meeting, 1976 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Bicentennial stamp, 1976 (Box S20)
  - Phi Beta Kappa. NC State University application, 1992 (Box S21)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1994 and 2005 (Box S21)
    Council reports, newsletters.
  - Phi Beta Kappa Associates, 1970-1975 (Box S21)
    Re: George Seward.
  - Phi Beta Kappa. University of San Francisco application, 2000 (Box S21)
  - Piedmont University Center of NC, 1964-1965 (Box S21)
  - Planned Parenthood of Orange/Durham Counties, 1999-2002 (Box S21)
    Re: Choice Affairs fundraising.
  - Political involvement opposing nuclear armament, 1958-1984 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement re: US Commission on Civil Rights, 1983 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement re: National Endowment for the Humanities, 1984 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement supporting the Mary McLeod Bethune Museum, 1984 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement supporting economic sanctions against South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement opposing John Agresto's appointment as US Archivist, 1986 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement opposing Robert Bork's nomination to the US Supreme Court, 1987 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement supporting Jackson and Dukakis in the US Presidential Election, 1988 (Box S21)
  - Political involvement opposing Clarence Thomas's nomination to the US Supreme Court, 1991, 2 folders (Box S21)
  - Political involvement opposing the Gulf War, 1991 (Box S21)
  - Pope House (Raleigh, NC), 2000-2002 (Box S21)
  - President's Advisory Board on Ambassadorial Appointments unsolicited nominations, 1977-1980 (Box S21)
  - President's Advisory Board on Ambassadorial Appointments posts, nominees, and general correspondence, 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box S21)
  - President's Task Force on International Education final report, 1965 (Box S21)
  - Protect Historic America. Co-Chairman, 1994 (Box S21)
    Opposing a Disney theme park in Virginia.
  - PUSH for Excellence, 1980-1985, 2 folders (Box S21)
  - Radio America: American Studies Center. Mr. Justice: Thurgood Marshall… cassette series, 1991-1992 (Box S21)
  - Radio Interviews correspondence, 1958-1982 (Box S21)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1958-1979 (Box S21)
  - Rutgers University. Paul Robeson Cultural Center, 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box S21)
    Correspondence and publications.
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, 1951-1964, 1980-1982, 4 folders (Box S22)
    Syllabi, participant lists, correspondence and planning materials.
  - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies Board of Directors, 1991-2006 (Box S22)
  - San Francisco Unified School District consultant, 1963-1975, 2 folders (Box S22)
  - Scholars and Citizens for Freedom of Information, 1980 (Box S22)
  - Separate But Equal television production advisor, 1989-1991 (Box S22)
  - Shakti for Children (Durham) Xanadu Project, 1996-1998, 2 folders (Box S22)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Alpha Tau Boule, 1984-2005, 3 folders (Box S22)
  - Sigma Pi Phi Fraternity membership directories, 1986-1995 (Box S22)
  - Slave Ship Replica Project, 1993-1994 (Box S22)
  - Smithsonian Institution policy papers and reports, 1991-1992 (Box S22)
  - Smithsonian Institution Folklife Festival, 1995-2006 (Box S22)
  - Social Science Research Council. Committee on Grants-In-Aid, 1956-1961 (Box S22)
  - Society of American Historians, 1950-2008 (Box S22)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference, 1961 (Box S22)
    Materials re: Executive Order against segregation.
  - Southern Growth Policies Board consultant, 1980-1981 (Box S22)
  - Southern Historians of the Early American Republic conference, 1993 (Box S22)
  - Southern Historical Association, 1941-1994, 2006, 2 folders (Box S22)
    General correspondence, meeting agendas, and programs.
  - Southern Historical Association research materials, 2004 (Box S23)
  - Southern Historical Association correspondence with Bennett Wall, 1952-1988 (Box S23)
  - Southern Historical Association constitution revision, 1971-1973 (Box S23)
  - Southern Historical Association presidency, 1970-1971 (Box S23)
  - Southern Justice Institute, 1989-1992 (Box S23)
    Formerly the Christic Institute South.
  - Southern Regional Education Board reports, 1998 (Box S23)
  - Southern Regional Council, 1998-2000 (Box S23)
  - St. Joseph's Historic Foundation (Durham), 1991 (Box S23)
  - Stuyvesant Community Center Board of Directors, 1961-1964 (Box S23)
  - Survival Series Television Program consultant, 1978-1979 (Box S23)
  - Teaching Tolerance (Southern Poverty Law Center), 1991-1995 (Box S23)
  - Television programs (general) consultant, 1964-1982 (Box S23)
  - Time-Life Exhibit on the American Negro correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box S23)
  - Thomas Day Education Project, 1995-2000 (Box S23)
    Two CDs containing electronic media have been separated from this folder. Please contact Research Services for assistance accessing those items.
  - Trumpet of Conscience (Durham), 1990-1996 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Historical Society, 1998-2000 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Public Schools, 1975 (Box S23)
    Narrator, The Life of Booker T. Washington.
  - Tulsa Race Riot Commission, 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Race Riot Commission Reconciliation ceremony, 2000 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Race ERiot Commission press, research, 2000 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Race Riot Commission draft report, 1999-2000 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Race Riot Commission analysis by Franklin and Scott Ellsworth, 2000 (Box S23)
  - Tulsa Race Riot lawsuit, 2003-2005, 5 folders (Box S23)
    Includes Franklin's statements, legal complaint, consultation with Charles Ogletree, press, and other related materials.
  - Tulsa Race Riot lawsuit, 2003, 4 folders (Box S24)
  - Tulsa's Burning documentary project proposal, 1999 (Box S24)
  - 21st Century Commission on African American Males, 1991-1992 (Box S24)
  - UNC TV: North Carolina, An American Portrait project proposal, 1998 (Box S24)
  - UN Commission for International Cooperation, 1965 (Box S24)
  - UNESCO conference, Belgrade, 1980 (Box S24)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1949-1981 (Box S24)
  - United Negro College Fund. Chicago Steering Committee, 1965-1979 (Box S24)
  - Unlikely Heroes film project, 1990 (Box S24)
  - US Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy personnel materials, 1977-1982 (Box S24)
  - US Advisory Commission on Public Diplomacy correspondence and memos, 1979-1987 (Box S24)
  - US Civil Rights Commission, 1961-1964 and 1995 (Box S24)
    Materials re: Franklin's report.
  - US Civil War Center Advisory Board, 1999-2002 (Box S24)
  - US Delegation to Zanzibar, 1963-1964 (Box S24)
    Celebrating Zanzibar's independence.
  - US Delegation to Zanzibar, independence celebrations, black-and-white photographs, 1963 (Box S26)
    In December 1963, Zanzibar gained its independence from the British Empire. JHF was part of the U.S. Delegation sent to join the celebration. The five 6 1/2 x 8 1/2 inch photos, taken by an unknown photographer, show a welcome arch, with "Uhuru," "Karibuni," the year 1963, and two silhouette maps of Zanzibar and Pemba islands; native and English officials seated on a stage while a speech is given; dances and celebrations; and the 19th century waterfront Sultan's palace in Zanzibar (Beit al-Sahel).
  - US House of Representatives. Liberal Project, 1959-1960 (Box S24)
    Re: Racial Equality.
  - US International Communication Agency reports, 1980-1981 (Box S24)
  - US National Slavery Museum Board of Directors project proposals, 2003-2004 (Box S24)
  - US Senate Judiciary Committee, 1987 (Box S24)
    Hearing on the nomination of Robert Bork to US Supreme Court.
  - US Senate. Report on Senate Reception Room from John F. Kennedy, 1957 (Box S24)
  - University Club, Durham, 1992-1996, 2004 (Box S24)
  - University of California San Diego. Visiting Committee evaluating the History Dept., 1975 (Box S24)
  - University of Chicago Ryerson Lecturer, 1973-1975 (Box S24)
  - University of Chicago. JHF Portait project, 1999 (Box S24)
  - University of London. Anglo-American Historical Committee, 1954 and 1963 (Box S24)
  - University of Michigan Law School. Affirmative Action Lawsuit: Grutter vs. Bollinger, 2000-2001, 8 folders (Box S25)
    Expert reports, Franklin's deposition transcript, trial transcripts, other press coverage.
  - Video Dialog. Durham documentary, 2002-2003 (Box S25)
  - Virginia Foundation for Independence Colleges Advisory Committee, 1990-1991 (Box S25)
  - Virginia Tech University. History Department evaluator, 1993 (Box S25)
  - Walnut Grove Colored School restoration project, 1990s (Box S25)
  - Walter Mondale for President, 1984 (Box S25)
  - WEB DuBois Memorial Park, 1958-1970 (Box S25)
  - WETA. A. Philip Randolph documentary, 1990-1996, 3 folders (Box S25)
    Correspondence, script, and publicity for PBS documentary airing 1994.
  - Westinghouse Broadcasting Co. The Great Ones radio series, 1965-1973 (Box S25)
  - WisdomWorks. A Journey Towards Peace, 1999-2001 (Box S25)
    Itineraries, editing, and publicity of Franklin and Tutu's documentary.
  - WisdomWorks. Race and Reconciliation, 2000 (Box S25)
    Photocopies of photographs.
  - Watergate/White House tapes affidavit, 1975 (Box S25)
  - WUNC Public Radio Community Advisory Council, 1986-1993 (Box S25)
  - William R. Kenan Charitable Trust, 1998 (Box S25)
  - York College Council on Academic Development, 1967-1970 (Box S25)
  - National Park System Advisory Board report, 2001 (Box S26)
- Writings (W), 1934-2009 and undated; 43 boxes
  The writings series includes materials from Franklin's books, articles, speeches, edited works, and miscellaneous writings, including his book reviews, interviews, outlines, and other essays. Files have been arranged by publication format into these various subseries, with detailed descriptions below.
  Certain unpublished writings are closed to use unless with explicit permission from the family. These have been segregated from other open writings.
  - Books, 1942-2005
    This subseries includes drafts, correspondence, proofs, and related correspondence and publicity from the publication of many of Franklin's books. Its materials are arranged chronologically by the books' initial release. The bulk of the materials relate to the later editions of From Slavery to Freedom, Franklin's biography on George Washington Williams, and Franklin's autobiography, Mirror to America.
    - The Free Negro in North Carolina, 1790-1860, 1942-1995
      Published by UNC Press in 1943 and in 1995 with a new foreword and bibliographic afterword by Franklin. Series contains mostly research material including Franklin's handwritten notes and archival documents. Also includes book reviews and correspondence ranging from 1943-1995.
      - Draft foreword to 1995 edition (Box W1)
      - Research material, 5 folders (Box W1)
      - Research material -- deed of Everett Mills (Box W1)
      - Research material -- 1850 census (Box W1)
      - Research material -- re. Miles Howard (Box W1)
      - Memorandum of Agreement, 1942 (Box W1)
      - Description of the book and announcement list (Box W1)
      - Publicity, 1943-1944 and 1995-1996 (Box W1)
      - Reviews, 1943-1944 and 1995-1996 (Box W1)
      - Correspondence, 1943-1995 (Box W1)
    - From Slavery to Freedom, 1943-2008
      Includes drafts from the 7th, 8th, and 9th editions, published in 1994, 2000, and 2005 respectively. The remainder of the materials, including correspondence, publicity, and book reviews, dates from the publication of the original edition in 1947. Book reviews and correspondence span from approximately 1943 to 2008. Correspondence includes exchanges with 6th, 7th, and 8th edition co-author Al Moss, fan mail, and notes expressing appreciation for the book. One disk containing electronic media has been separated from this subseries. Please contact Research Services for assistance accessing that item.
      - 7th edition preface (Box W1)
      - 7th edition, draft, folders 1-6 of 15 (Box W1)
      - 7th edition, draft, folders 7-15 of 15 (Box W2)
      - 7th edition correspondence and revisions, folders 1-2 of 3 (Box W2)
      - 7th edition correspondence and revisions, folder 3 of 3 (Box W3)
      - 7th edition, photographs and art work (Box W3)
      - 7th edition, copyright information, 2 folders (Box W3)
      - 7th edition, photographs of art work from Al Moss with 1993 letter (Box W3)
      - 7th edition, photographs with Al Moss, 1993-1996 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 1-10 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 2-5 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of preface-chapter 4 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 4-8 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 6-13 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 7-13 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 9-13 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapter 11 and chapter 17 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 14-18 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 14- 21 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 14- 20 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 19- 23 (Box W3)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 24- 25 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 22- 23 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, draft of chapters 22-24 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, captions lists, chapters 8-13 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, captions (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, information about captions (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, information about images and captions, Picture Research Consultants (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, preliminary style sheet, chapters 1-7 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, bibliographic information (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, information about illustrations (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, research material (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, news articles sent to Franklin from Al Moss, 5 folders (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, clippings from Al Moss sent to Franklin from Al Moss July 27, 1999 (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, list of charts and maps (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, notes on revisions and insertions, 2 folders (Box W4)
      - 8th edition, Aaron Douglas painting (Box W5)
      - 8th edition, Revised preface and bibliographic notes (Box W5)
      - 8th edition, notes on preface revisions (Box W5)
      - 8th edition, notes on chapter 25 (Box W5)
      - 8th edition, Al Moss and Franklin conference notes, 1998-1999 (Box W5)
      - 8th edition, "Gallery of Twentieth-Century African American Artists" (Box W5)
      - 9th edition, reviews of 8th edition and meeting agenda (Box W5)
      - Undated drafts, chapters 1-6 (Box W5)
      - Undated drafts, chapters 7-12 (Box W5)
      - Undated drafts, chapters 16-19 (Box W5)
      - Undated drafts (Box W5)
      - Publisher's guide and questionnaire (Box W5)
      - Book covers (Box W5)
      - "Biography of a Book," notes, drafts, etc. 1995 (Box W5)
      - Critical appraisals, suggestions, and revisions, 1980-1985 (Box W5)
      - Writing "From Slavery to Freedom," undated essay (Box W5)
      - Fiftieth anniversary celebration brochure, September 19-20, 1997 (Box W5)
      - The American Negro: A History (From Slavery to Freedom), publishing agreement, 1946 (Box W5)
      - Research material (Box W5)
      - Adoption reports, 1994-1998 (Box W5)
      - TV adaptation, 1972 (Box W5)
      - Teacher's guide and correspondence, 1979 (Box W5)
      - Book reviews, 1947-1988 and undated, 3 folders (Box W5)
      - Correspondence, 1943-1960, 2 folders (Box W6)